And there's a possiblity that what
we're looking for is in here.
-Yes, sir.
-Let's move!
What's really happening to him?
I spend my whole life
looking for that bomb.
Do you think Angelito got exposed
to that bomb's radiation?
Should I tell them?
Run!
Get inside the house!
Everything in their house!
Where are you going?
Everything will be okay.
We'll save your brother.
Sofie…
What happened?
-Come on.
-Huh?
What is going on?
Viktor Valtrovi.
Agent Sianong, the bomb squad
is on the way.
All right. Stay safe.
-Where is it?!
-Stop!
It's here!
We found what we're looking for!
Those are La Morte's men.
What should we do?
Bro, what's that?
Let's back off.
No, keep going.
Are you okay, sweetheart?
I'm okay.
You know, if you keep pacing like that,
you'll wear a hole in the floor.
I'm getting dizzy for the poor floor.
Viktor.
I'm just worried.
I'm so worried, my love.
Me too.
Hey.
It won't start. Hey, it's smoking.
Let's check it.
I think the radiator got hit.
Help me.
Let's cover it.
Easy.
We can't.
Why not?!
Chiara, we have protocols, right?
That's what the bomb squad is for.
They're trained to handle this.
They're not even here yet.
Then we'll do it ourselves. Let's go!
The tip was legit.
It's not our job or our mission
to retrieve that weapon
of mass destruction. Okay?
Our mission is to make sure
Angelito and Sofie are safe.
If they get that bomb, we're all dead!
If we can't even make sure
those two are safe,
we're also risking their lives.
Let's go, Angelito. Hurry.
Stay here.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
This can't happen.
What can't?
The bomb.
The bomb?
We can't let them get it.
I have a strong feeling
it shouldn't end up in their hands.
Sofie, come on.
You're not even sure that's what
your dad's agency is looking for.
Angelito, we have to do something.
We'll stay here.
We can't do that, Angelito.
We can't always play it safe.
Sometimes we have to take risks.
Do you know, Sofie,
how dangerous this is? Look!
They have so many guns.
It's way too dangerous!
Agent Dara, still nothing?
I've tried three radio channels.
Maybe they're just in a dead zone.
Sofie told me
the signal is weak over there.
I hope that's all it is.
Try a different frequency.
Team, please respond.
Mikoy!
Sianong!
This might be our only chance.
Don't you get it?
You're both right.
That's the problem.
If we were here for someone else,
this would've been easier.
But we're not.
Angelito is my brother.
And Sofie is General Ruiz's daughter.
We have to find them.
But we can't let that leave either.
Looks like they're leaving. Yes.
-They're leaving?
-Yes.
Thank goodness.
What do you mean?
We're finally getting out of here.
We still have to find
Laurence and Luisa Mae.
Who knows what happened to them.
Something?
Sofie.
If we do anything else,
we might never make it out of here.
Who knows what could happen to us.
You know what, Angelito?
You're such a coward!
Sofie!
You can't do that!
Come on, hurry!
Hurry!
Angelito!
What's that?
Stop!
-Mikoy!
-Mikoy, wait!
Chiara!
Let's go!
Go. I'll handle the bomb!
It's um…
a wild boar.
Hurry up!
Hurry.
What?
Have you found them?
-They're not here.
-Not here either.
Let's check over here.
What a shame.
Angelito. Hurry up.
Let's stay here for now.
Come on, Angelito.
Hurry up.
Come here.
What?
Did you see them?
-They're not here.
-They disappeared.
Let's split up.
You go that way. We'll go this way.
Let's go!
Brusko.
Keep your voice down.
Lady Amor.
Yes. Follow me.
Okay.
Come on, Angelito.
Come on, come on.
Easy now.
Over here.
All right.
Where are we going?
Your parents will be so happy.
So much has happened.
The bomb is here.
Ms. Italy took it.
Now you're here too, huh?
Was this your plan all along?
You're the one who tipped them off.
Because Viktor never told me anything.
Why do you look so angry?
Why would I be angry?
Yes, why would you be?
Peace! We're on the same side!
-They came this way, right?
-Yes.
-Angelito!
-Sofie!
-Where are you?
Sofie.
They went through here, right?
Yes!
Sofie!
Angelito!
Where are you two? Come out!
Sofie!
Take cover! Take cover! Mikoy!
-I'm out of ammo.
-Me too.
What are we gonna do, Viktor?
Sianong!